one of the best things about strong
curves is that I included beginning
exercises intermediate exercises and
advanced exercises and I have programs
for beginners for intermediat and for
advanced and I have progressions I
outline the progressions along the way
so you can be a beginner and you know
where to start with strong curves and
you can be the most advanced you know
female fitness competitor and and strong
curves works for them too it works for
everyone it's a it's a a program that
will stand the test of time because it
has all the best
exercises and and and the program is
designed for
anyone I'm known around the world as the
glute guy and I the glute specialist and
and I've been doing this for so long I
can just glance at any you know routine
and I just I know if that's going to
work the glutes or not if it's going to
cause the glutes to reshape you're not
what are you doing for the glutes a
couple sets of body weight lunges that's
not going to reshape anyone's glutes ABS
might be made in the kitchen
but glutes are made in the gym to me the
Brazilians have it right they'll hire a
trainer and do an hourong glute workout
and and no upper body no abs and their
bodies look amazing because they focus
on the glutes anyone who works out you
know year after year who committed to
Fitness you know the best exercises but
you need variety everyone needs Variety
in their programs and strong curves has
hundreds of exercises to choose from we
offer so many different glute exercises
that you know never get bored you your
glutes will never be bored of the same
thing you have plenty of variety plenty
of options to choose from and plenty of
ways to tailor the workout whether
you're training at home whether you're
training in a gym whether you have just
your body weight to work with if you
have dumbbells kettle bells bands free
weights barbells um you know the strong
curves can accommodate
anyone the byproduct of glute training
is these glute exercis are the hardest
exercises metabolically so when you
train the glutes you're training the
biggest muscle groups in the body you
know the glutes the quadriceps the
hamstrings and so the metabolism gets
raised and then you get lean all over so
focusing on the glutes is the
centerpiece of any any female's program
[Music]